<custom-action actionType="CitrixTextWait" enabled="false" isHit="true"
    name="textwait" uid="efa10939-2ff3-400b-aba9-98009146b402">
    <description>This Action waits for text to appear in a window (by filling parameter "windowName") OR in a specific region (by filling parameter "windowRect").

Possible parameters are:&#xd;
- windowName (optional): Window name, that can be a regular expression. It can contain a NeoLoad variable. If a regular expression is used, then any characters considered as reserved need to be escaped according to the regex syntax standard (for example characters \|?*+()[].). For example, "Document.*" will match any window name starting with string "Document", and "Document \(\d+\)" will match any window name with "Document" followed by a number in parenthesis, such as "Document (1)" or "Document (10)". If empty, the working area is the full screen.&#xd;
- windowRect (optional): Region of the window in the format: [poxX,poxY,width,height]. It will be absolute coordinate if no "windowName", or relative coordinate if "windowName" is specified or empty if full screenshot.&#xd;
- text (required): Text to look for, can be a regular expression. It can contain a NeoLoad variable. If a regular expression is used, then any characters considered as reserved need to be escaped according to the regex syntax standard (for example characters \|?*+()[].). For example, "keyword" will match if the extracted content starts with "keyword", ".*keyword.*" will match if the single line extracted content contains "keyword", and "(.|\n)*keyword(.|\n)*" will match if the multi line extracted content contains "keyword".&#xd;
- inverseColor (required): When recognizing white text over black background, set it to true to best result. Default value is "false".&#xd;
- pollingDelayInMs (required): Delay in milliseconds between each check. Default value is "500".&#xd;
- waitTimeoutInMs (required): Maximum timeout in milliseconds to wait. Default value is "60000".</description>
    <custom-action-parameter name="windowName" type="TEXT" value=""/>
    <custom-action-parameter name="windowRect" type="TEXT" value="[268,118,86,22]"/>
    <custom-action-parameter name="text" type="TEXT" value="Interaction ID:"/>
    <custom-action-parameter name="inverseColor" type="TEXT" value="false"/>
    <custom-action-parameter name="pollingDelayInMs" type="TEXT" value="500"/>
    <custom-action-parameter name="waitTimeoutInMs" type="TEXT" value="60000"/>
    <responsePageFileDescription>recorded-responses/res_0f609f3d-07ca-42a7-8878-930415779727</responsePageFileDescription>
    <screenshotFileDescription>team/vus/@tripleplay_@change_@downgrade_001/%resources%/recorded-screenshots/sc_0f609f3d-07ca-42a7-8878-930415779727.0.png</screenshotFileDescription>
</custom-action>
